akosha.com 2014-09-20

# Privacy Policy | Akosha

  * We hold all information you provide to us in absolute privacy. 
  * We will never share your name, e-mail address or personal information with any third party except to resolve your complaint, unless specifically authorized by you. 
  * We use a secure payment gateway to process your payments. We do not receive any details of your credit card, debit card or net-banking account. 
  * We never sell or rent our mailing list - your trust is more important to us than anything else. 
  * Only authorized and background-checked employees may access your information, and only on need-to-know basis. 
  * All employees are required to adhere to our strict privacy policies and non-disclosure agreements. Any employee who violates these agreements is subject to termination and other measures, including criminal prosecution. 

#### Traffic data

Through a combination of both internal and third party tracking codes as well as cookies, the following categories of information are tracked when a visitor enters the web site: 

  * IP address
  * Domain server
  * Type of computer used to access the site
  * Type of web browser (collectively 'Traffic Data')

Akosha.com uses such data for general marketing purposes and in order to help enhance customer experience on the website. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags also known as single pixel GIFs or web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous.

#### Personal Information

In order for each customer to access and utilize Akosha.com's products and services, Akosha.com requires each customer to provide us with personal information ('Personally Identifiable Information'). We keep your Personally Identifiable Information private and will not share it with third parties unless you specifically approve of the disclosure, or if Akosha.com is required by law to comply with a valid legal requirement such as law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order. However, data and meta-data related to your complaint may also be aggregated, assessed, analyzed and used for improving our ability to provide our service as well as to brands which may use this information for their marketing or customer service improvement purposes. This data may also be used in presenting better information, advertisement or offers to you in the future. 

#### Your Consent

By providing your personal information to Akosha.com in a questionnaire, application, form or similar document or service, you explicitly agree and give us your consent to call you regarding your complaint or any other similar service which is provided by us. You further agree and consent to be bound by the terms of our Privacy Policy. 

#### Communication to you or about you

We collect your Personally Identifiable Information in order to serve you better. We may send you newsletters with consumer rights related information, other promotional emails or SMSs about the status and updates on your complaint or issue. If you do not wish to receive our newsletter after the first time, you can easily click unsubscribe at the bottom of the email and we will not send you any newsletters after that. 

We reserve the right to display certain information about you on our website including your name, the company against whom you have complained, the kind of complaint and other such data which does not identify you specifically. We will obviously share all the details of your complaint with the company against whom the complaint has been made unless you specifically request us to do otherwise. 

#### Third Party Websites

Akosha.com may maintain links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we are not responsible for the Privacy Practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the Privacy Policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies. 

#### Data Security

We strive to make certain that our servers and connections incorporate the latest encryption and security devices. To prevent unauthorized access, we have implemented physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. Documents are delivered to you either via priority mail or via e-mail. 

#### Questions/Queries

Any questions, queries or clarifications regarding our Privacy Policy can be directed to: support@akosha.com. Alternatively, you can call us at 0120-380-3011.
